Joseph Oluwadara

BLOCKCHAIN SECURITY ENGINEER

PROFILE

Smart Contract Engineer and Auditor with vast experience in writing Solidity smart contracts and deeper understanding of the EVM.I use Foundry, Hardhat and Remix for smart contract writing, testing and fuzz testing. I also use automated tools like Slither and Echidna. I have experience working with different smart contracts, including: AMMs, Fungible and Nonfungible tokens, Staking contract, Account Abstraction, Vaults, Proxies and Upgradeable contracts, as well as building personalized smart contracts. I am a security minded engineer and I currently do smart contract audits at Code4rena and Sherlock . I also participate in different CTFs and I have completed a few such as Ethernaut from Openzeppelin, DamnVunerableDefi, Secureum Bootcamp and more.

EXPERIENCE

Smart Contract Auditor

February 2023 - Present

Auditing Smart Contracts in Code4rena, ImmuneFi and Sherlock

Blockchain Developer (Contract)

Astra Metaverse

September 2022 - Present

- Created an ERC 1155 token smart contract and minter
- Created a Metaverse Marketplace smart contract

Lagos, Nigeria +2348116361700 jsatimehin@gmail.com Github LinkedIn Twitter Website

SKILLS

Solidity
Assembly: YUL
EthersJS & Web3JS
Foundry & Hardhat
Slither
JavaScript & Typescript
The Graph
Rust
NextJS & React

COMMUNITIES

- Developer Dao Member
- Polygon Guid Lagos Member
- Code4rena
- Sherlock
- Web3SecurityDA0

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE,

MATHEMATICS

Federal University of Agriculture, Abeokuta

2018 - 2022

• Writing APIs to connect with the smart contracts on the blockchain

Blockchain Developer

COLLECT WAVES

May 2022 - December 2022

- Created & Tested an Music NFT smart Contract
- Designed an NFT market place smart contract and NFT minter
- Writing APIs to connect with the smart contracts on the blockchain
- Creation of Tokens.

FullStack Blockchain Developer

LivingStone Blockchain IT

January 2022 - August 2022

- Writing and testing smart contracts on the EVM compatible blockchains
- Building a UI that interacts with the blockchain with web3.js
- Created a Decentralized Exchange to swap tokens
- Interviewed and lead the daily activities of a team of Developers

Frontend Solutions Developer

IPI SOLUTIONS

May 2021 - February 2022

- Built a Document Management System around Microsoft Sharepoint using Angular and Typescript
- Created and Modified 3000+ Document Libraries